const unit5Problems = [{
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 5.1 ----------------------------------
        //15
        id: 107,
        question: "Find the points on the graph of ${\\it y} = {\\it x}^2$ that are closest to the point $(0, 3)$.",
        answer: "(- sqrt (5/2), 5/2), (sqrt (5/2), 5/2)",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //19
        id: 108,
        question: "A farmer plans to fence a rectangular pasture adjacent to a river. The side of the pasture along the river does not need fencing. The pasure is $405,000$ square meters. What is least amount of fencing needed to satisfy these requirements?",
        answer: "1800",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //25
        id: 109,
        question: "A rectangle is bounded by the $\\it x$-axis and the semicircle ${\\it y} = \\sqrt{25-{\\it x}^2}$. (2 of the rectangle's vertices lie on the $\\it x$-axis and the other 2 lie on the semicircle.) What dimensions should the rectangle have to maximize its area? (Enter your answer as a comma separated pair of values, smaller value first.)",
        answer: "(5 sqrt 2)/2, 5 sqrt 2",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //39
        id: 110,
        question: "An offshore oil well is $2$ kilometers off the coast. The refinery is $4$ kilometers down the coast. Laying pipe in the ocean is twice as expensive as laying it on land. How much pipe (in kilometers) should be lain on land in order to minimize the cost?",
        answer: "4 - 2/ sqrt 3",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //53
        id: 111,
        question: "Find the point on the graph of $16{\\it x} = {\\it y}^2$ that is closest to the point $(6, 0)$.",
        answer: "(0, 0)",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.1",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 5.2 ----------------------------------
    {
        //93
        id: 112,
        question: "Find the average rate of change of the function ${\\it f(x)} = \\dfrac{-1}{\\it x}$ over the interval $[1, 2]$.",
        answer: "1/2",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //95b
        id: 113,
        question: "A coin is dropped from the top of a building that is $1362$ feet tall. Find the average velocity of the coin on the interval $[1, 2]$. Use the position function ${\\it s(t)} = -16{\\it t}^2 + {\\it v}_0{\\it t} + {\\it s}_0$.",
        answer: "-48",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //95e
        id: 114,
        question: "A coin is dropped from the top of a building that is $1362$ feet tall. Find the velocity of the coin at impact. Use the position function ${\\it s(t)} = -16{\\it t}^2 + {\\it v}_0{\\it t} + {\\it s}_0$. Round to the nearest 3 decimal places.",
        answer: "-292.242",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //117
        id: 115,
        question: "The velocity of an object is ${\\it v(t)} = 36 - {\\it t}^2$, for $0 \\leq {\\it t} \\leq 6$. Find the acceleration of the object when ${\\it t} = 3$.",
        answer: "-6",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //117
        id: 116,
        question: "True or False: An object is slowing down if its velocity and acceleration have different signs.",
        answer: "True",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.2",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 5.3 ----------------------------------
    {
        //11
        id: 117,
        question: "For the function ${\\it f(x)} = -{\\it x}^2 + 3\\it x$, determine if Rolle's Theorem can be applied on the closed interval $[0, 3]$. If it can be applied, find all values of $\\it c$ in the open interval $(0, 3)$ such that ${\\it f\\>'(c)} = 0$.",
        answer: "c = 3/2",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //19
        id: 118,
        question: "For the function ${\\it f(x)} = \\sin \\it x$, determine if Rolle's Theorem can be applied on the closed interval $[0, 2\\pi]$. If it can be applied, find all values of $\\it c$ in the open interval $(0, 2\\pi)$ such that ${\\it f\\>'(c)} = 0$.",
        answer: "c = pi/2, c = 3pi/2",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //41
        id: 119,
        question: "For the function ${\\it f(x)} = {\\it x}^3 + 2{\\it x} + 4$, determine if the Mean Value Theorem can be applied on the closed interval $[-1, 0]$. If it can be applied, find all values of $\\it c$ in the open interval $(-1, 0)$ such that ${\\it f\\>'(c)} = \\dfrac{\\it f(b)-f(a)}{\\it b-a}$.",
        answer: "c = -(sqrt 3)/3",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //45
        id: 120,
        question: "For the function ${\\it f(x)} = |2{\\it x}+1|$, determine if the Mean Value Theorem can be applied on the closed interval $[-1, 3]$. If it can be applied, find all values of $\\it c$ in the open interval $(-1, 3)$ such that ${\\it f\\>'(c)} = \\dfrac{\\it f(b)-f(a)}{\\it b-a}$. If it cannot be applied, enter 'N/A'.",
        answer: "N/A",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //53b
        id: 121,
        question: "The height of an object $\\it t$ seconds after it is dropped from a height of $300$ meters is ${\\it s(t)} = -4.9{\\it t}^2 + 300$. Use the Mean Value Theorem to find the time during the first $3$ seconds of fall, when the instantaneous velocity equals the average velocity over the first $3$ seconds.",
        answer: "t = 1.5",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.3",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    },
    //--------------------------------------------SECTION 5.4 ----------------------------------
    {
        //9
        id: 122,
        question: "Evaluate the limit: $\\lim_{{\\it x} \\to 6} \\dfrac{\\sqrt{{\\it x}+10}-4}{{\\it x}-6} $",
        answer: "1/8",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //19
        id: 123,
        question: "Evaluate the limit: $\\lim_{{\\it x} \\to 0^+} \\dfrac{e^{\\it x}-(1+{\\it x})}{{\\it x}^3} $",
        answer: "infinity",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //23
        id: 124,
        question: "Evaluate the limit: $\\lim_{{\\it x} \\to 0} \\dfrac{\\sin 3\\it x}{\\sin 5\\it x} $",
        answer: "3/5",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //35
        id: 125,
        question: "Evaluate the limit: $\\lim_{{\\it x} \\to \\infty} \\dfrac{\\ln \\it x}{{\\it x}^2} $",
        answer: "0",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }, {
        //105
        id: 126,
        question: "Find the values of $\\it a$ and $\\it b$ such that $\\lim_{{\\it x} \\to 0} \\dfrac{{\\it a} - \\cos \\it bx}{{\\it x}^2} = 2 $",
        answer: "a = 1, b = +/-2",
        unit: 5,
        topic: "5.4",
        tags: [],
        solution: "sample solution"
    }

];
    
    export default unit5Problems;